A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Commissioner of the Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1984-1994, 2004-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1984-1994, 2006.
  - 1984-1993 (bulk 1990-1993) (Accession 36853)., 58 cu. ft. (58 boxes)
    - Virginia Dark-Fired Tobacco Commission, 1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Dark-Fired Tobacco Commission, 1977-1988. (Box 13)
    - Viticultural Technical Advisory Committee, 1984-1991. (Box 13)
    - Plant Pollination Advisory Board #2, 1983-1991. (Box 14)
    - Feed IndustryAdvisory Committee, 1973-1991. (Box 14)
    - Virginia Food Processors Advisory Committee, 1977-1990. (Box 14)
    - Pesticide Advisory Committee, 1987-1991. (Box 14)
    - Pesticide Advisory Committee #2, 1978-1987. (Box 14)
    - sAnnual report, 1988-1990. (Box 14)
    - VDACS Board meeting, 1992 July 9. (Box 14)
    - Food and Drug Admistration, 1990-1991. (Box 14)
    - Governor's Office, 1990. (Box 14)
    - Governor's Office, 1991. (Box 14)
    - Governor's Young Farmer Award, 1987-1990. (Box 14)
    - Governor's Initiative on Rural Development, 1990. (Box 14)
    - Governor's Cup Competition, 1990 Sept. (Box 14)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1990-1991. (Box 14)
    - Governor's Transportation Planning and Environmental Review Initiative, 1991. (Box 14)
    - Briefing - Lt. Governor Wilder, 1988. (Box 14)
    - Governor's Trade Mission, 1990. (Box 14)
    - Groundwater, 1990. (Box 14)
    - Ground/Wave Emergency Network, 1989-1990. (Box 14)
    - Horses (general information), 1987-1990. (Box 14)
    - HACCP Strategy Paper, 1990. (Box 14)
    - Interstate Pest Control Compact, 1989-1990. (Box 15)
    - DIT Implementation Status Report, 1990. (Box 15)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (DIT), 1989-1991. (Box 15)
    - Intellectual Property, 1989. (Box 15)
    - Integrating Agricultural Marketing Programs - DIT, 1989-1990. (Box 15)
    - Mid-Atlantic Agricultural Export and Trade Policy Center, 1990. (Box 15)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1987-1990. (Box 15)
    - Japanese External Trade Organization (JETRO), 1990. (Box 15)
    - Japan Large Kernel Ground Nut Importer, 1982-1987.. (Box 15)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 1989-1990. (Box 15)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Office of, 1984-1991. (Box 15)
    - Metric Conversion Act, 1985-1989. (Box 15)
    - Mobil Oil Corp, 1990. (Box 15)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA), 1990. (Box 15)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1990. (Box 15)
    - Apples treated with DDAs, 1990. (Box 15)
    - Americans for Safe Food, 1988. (Box 15)
    - Apple Spray Residue Task Force, 1989-1990. (Box 15)
    - Attorney General, Office of the, 1987-1991. (Box 15)
    - American Marketing Services, 1984-1990. (Box 15)
    - Agribusiness Council, Virginia, 1990. (Box 15)
    - Animal Damage Control, 1989-1990. (Box 15)
    - Virginia Sheep Federation, 1989. (Box 15)
    - Beef Expo, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Commissioner's Correspondence (Clinton V. Turner), 1992. (Box 16)
    - Secretary of Economic Development (Lawrence H. Framme, III) correspondence, 1992. (Box 16)
    - Deputy Secretary of Economic Develpment (Michael Green and William P. Dickenson) correspondence, 1992. (Box 16)
    - Commissioner's Correspondence #2 (Clinton V. Turner), 1992 July. (Box 17)
    - Commissioner's Correspondence #4 (Clinton V. Turner), 1993 May-June. (Box 17)
    - Commissioner's Correspondence #5 (Clinton V. Turner), 1993 June. (Box 17)
    - Commissioner's Correspondence #6 (Clinton V. Turner), 1993 June-July. (Box 17)
    - Commissioner's Correspondence #7 (Clinton V. Turner), 1993 July-Sept. (Box 17)
    - Commissioner's Correspondence #8 (Clinton V. Turner), 1993 Sept-Oct. (Box 17)
    - Deputy Commissioner's Correspondence #2 (Donald G. Blankenship), 1992 July-Sept. (Box 17)
    - Deputy Commissioner's Correspondence #3 (Donald G. Blankenship), 1992 Sept-Dec. (Box 17)
    - Commissioner's Office - Miscellaneous, 1992. (Box 18)
    - Division Director Memos (Blankenship), 1992. (Box 18)
    - Hazelwood, Moyer W., 1992. (Box 18)
    - Jackson, Karen E. (Human Resources), 1992. (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resources, 1991-1992. (Box 18)
    - Hill, Herbert H., 1992. (Box 18)
    - Seward, Roy E., 1992. (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy and Planning #3, 1992. (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy and Planning #2, 1992. (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy and Planning #1, 1992. (Box 18)
    - Mainframe, 1992. (Box 18)
    - Martin, T. R., 1992. (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous - Purchasing and Supply, 1992. (Box 18)
    - Blakemore, Betty W., 1992. (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Affairs, 1992. (Box 18)
    - Consumer Affairs - proposed name change, 1993. (Box 19)
    - Consumer letters #3, 1992 Oct-Dec. (Box 19)
    - Consumer letters #2, 1992 Apr-Oct. (Box 19)
    - Consumer letters #1, 1992 Jan-Apr. (Box 19)
    - Consumer Forum, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Strategic Planning, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous - other agencies, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Layne, Ronald K., 1992. (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous - Administration, 1991-1992. (Box 19)
    - Altschul, B. J., 1992. (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous - Communications, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Garey, Louis M., 1992. (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous - Facilities, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Halbleib, M. C., 1992. (Box 19)
    - Mahone, James E., 1992. (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Jeffries, Larry, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Tubbs, Mark D., 1992. (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous - Dairy and Foods, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Dell'Aria, Arthur D., 1992. (Box 19)
    - Organic Food, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Dairy and Foods Work Group, 1991-1992. (Box 19)
    - Johnson, Robert, 1992-1993. (Box 19)
    - Sims, William E. #2, 1992. (Box 19)
    - Sims, William E., 1992. (Box 19)
    - Miscellaeous - Animal Health, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Animal Laws - Comprehensive, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Annual Report - Division of Animal Health, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Animal Health fees, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Incinerator - Richmond Lab, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Fees - Animal Health and Seed Testing, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Equine Viral Arteritis (EVA), 1992. (Box 20)
    - Meat Certification Agreement, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Blue Tongue, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Animal Health Laboratory Advisory Committee, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Bureau of Meat and Poultry Inspection, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Pseudorabies Virus Committee, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Gomperts, Robert E., 1992. (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous - Marketing, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Annual Report - Division of Marketing, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1992. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Soybean Board, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA), 1992. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Thoroughbred Association, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Southern U.S. Trade Association (SUSTA), 1992. (Box 21)
    - Toxic Substances Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Secretary's Responses - Referral File #3, 1992 June-Dec. (Box 21)
    - Secretary's Responses - Referral File #2, 1992 Mar-June. (Box 21)
    - Secretary's Responses - Referral File #1, 1992 Jan-Mar. (Box 21)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Congress, U.S., 1992. (Box 21)
    - Conservation Directory, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Corn, White, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Council of Farm Cooperatives, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Delmarva Poultry Industry, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Delaware Poultry Indemnity Plan MOU, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Information Management System, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Letters of Credit, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Crop Field Day, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Disaster Assistance, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Duke University, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Early Retirement, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Eastern Shore Farmers Market, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Employee Productivity Incentive Fund, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Employee Suggestion Award, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Employee Orientation, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Environment, Council on the, 1992. (Box 21)
    - Environment, Council on the, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1992. (Box 22)
    - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Epistat, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Executive Institute, Virginia, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Agricultural Export Center (Blackstone), 1992. (Box 22)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) Task Force, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Fairs - Virginia Regional and County, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Fair - State of Virginia, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Farm Bureau, Virginia, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Farmers Market Nutrition Program, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Farmers Market Project, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Farm Loans, 1992. (Box 22)
    - General Fund Proposed Regulations, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Federal Issues, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Food and Agriculture Council of Virginia, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Food and Libation Association of Virginia (FLAVA), 1992. (Box 22)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Food Safety, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Forest Service, U.S., 1992. (Box 22)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Friends of the Industry of Agriculture, 1992. (Box 22)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - General Assembly, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Governor's Office, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Health, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Hog Farmers, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Honey Bees, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Horse Center, Virginia, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Horse Council, Virginia, 1992. (Box 22)
    - House Agriculture Committee, VDACS Report to, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Incineration - Consolidated Labs, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Information Management, Council on, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - International Organization for Standards (ISO), 1992. (Box 22)
    - Interior, U.S. Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Internal Auditor, 1992. (Box 22)
    - International Initiative, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Kellogg Grant, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Kenaf Project, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Laboratories - VDACS and DCL, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Lay off, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1992. (Box 22)
    - Legislative - Consumer Affairs, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Legislative Proposals (1993), 1992. (Box 22)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Legislative Session, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Legislative Studies, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Liaison Office, Virginia, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Lims Tiger Teams (DCLS), 1992. (Box 22)
    - Market Promotion Program (MPP), 1992. (Box 22)
    - Market Promotion Program (MPP) - USDA, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Direct Marketing, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Meat and Poultry, 1992. (Box 22)
    - MOU - VDACS and Air Pollution Board, 1992. (Box 22)
    - MOU - Pair and Administrative Information Systems, 1992. (Box 22)
    - MOU - VDACS and Economic Development, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Mental Health, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Milk Commission, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - National Aquaculture Act, 1992. (Box 22)
    - Natural Resource, Secretary of, 1992. (Box 22)
    - News Releases, 1992. (Box 22)
    - New Users, 1992. (Box 22)
    - News Releases - USDA, 1992. (Box 22)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1992. (Box 23)
    - Nutrition Labeling Education Act, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Out of State Blanket Appropriation, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Pesticide and Groundwater Management Plan, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Petition - ABC Board Farm Winery Law, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Pittsylvania County Chamber of Commerce, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Plant Pollination Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Poultry Federation, Virginia, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Prompt Payment, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Public Safety, Secretary of, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Purcell, John, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Recommendations to the Governor, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Recycling, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Regulations Review, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Report to the Governor, 1992. (Box 23)
    - HJR 73, 1992. (Box 23)
    - HJR 205, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Retreat - SMT, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Rocco Farm, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Rural Development Committee, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Rural Economic Development, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Savings Bond Campaign, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Scholarship Trust (G.P. Meade), 1992. (Box 23)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Senators/Congressmen - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Senate Committee on Agriculture, Conservation and Natural Resources, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Sexual Harassment Policy, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Soil and Water Conservation, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Southern States, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Southern Legislative Conference, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Southside Economic Development Committee, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Southside Virginia Producers Coop, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Southside Virginia Farmers Market, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Southeast Virginia Farmers Market, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Southwest Virginia Farmers Market, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Stage II Vapor Recovery, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Strategic Planning, 1992. (Box 23)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Virginia State University, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on the Environment, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on Food Safety, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on Information Functions, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on International Standards and Global Trade, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on Laboratory Services, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on Cooperation for Land Grant Universities, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on Legal Services, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on Pesticide and Groundwater, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Road Signing Feasibility Study, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Task Force on Strategic Planning, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Talking Points, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Talking Points - House Agriculture Committee, 1992. (Box 23)
    - J.R. Thomas Camp, Inc., 1992. (Box 23)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 23)
    - USDA - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 23)
    - USDA - Food and Drug Administration, 1992. (Box 23)
    - USDA - Food Safety and Inspection, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Vendors, 1992. (Box 23)
    - VDACS - Virginia Tech Task Force, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Voicemnail, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Warrenton Laboratory, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Water Control Board, State, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Water Protection Permit, 1992. (Box 23)
    - Alternate Work Schedules, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Wetlands, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Wytheville Laboratories, 1992. (Box 24)
    - ACS, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council, 1992. (Box 24)
    - National Appaloosa Horse Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia State Apple Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Apple Growers Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Aquaculture Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Awards Committee, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Carolina-Virginia Milk Producers Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Cattlemens Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Chippokes Plantation, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Corn Growers Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - National Corn Growers Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virgina Crop Improvement Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia State Dairymen Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Deer Farming Advisory Committee, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Egg Council, 1992. (Box 24)
    - EEO Advisory Committee, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Farmers Market, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Feed Industry Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Food Processors Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Goat and Mohair Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Governmental Employees Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Horse Industry Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Livestock Market Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Marine Products Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA), 1992. (Box 24)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) Honor Awards, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Recylcing Committee - VDACS, 1992. (Box 24)
    - American Saddlebred Horse Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Seed Potato Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - N.C. Seedmen's Association, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Small Growers Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Plant Pollination Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Radiation Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board, 1992. (Box 24)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade - Public Information Group, 1992-1993. (Box 25)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary, 1993. (Box 25)
    - Economic Development Plan, 1993. (Box 25)
    - Secretary of Economic Development(#4), 1993 Sept-Dec. (Box 25)
    - Secretary of Economic Development(#3), 1993 June-Oct. (Box 25)
    - Secretary of Economic Development (#2), 1993 Apr-July. (Box 25)
    - Secretary of Economic Development (#1), 1993 Jan-Apr. (Box 25)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade - William Dickinson (#3), 1993 Sept-Dec. (Box 25)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade - William Dickinson (#2), 1993 Apr-Nov. (Box 25)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade - William Dickinson (#1), 1993 Jan-Apr. (Box 25)
    - Deputy Secretary of Economic Development - Mike Green, 1993. (Box 25)
    - Commissioner Clinton V. Turner - correspondence (#11), 1993 Dec. (Box 25)
    - Commissioner Clinton V. Turner - correspondence (#10) 1993 Nov. (Box 25)
    - Commissioner Clinton V. Turner - correspondence (#9), 1993 Oct. (Box 26)
    - Commissioner Clinton V. Turner - correspondence (#3), 1993 Apr-May. (Box 26)
    - Commissioner Clinton V. Turner - correspondence (#2), 1993 Feb-Apr. (Box 26)
    - Reader file, 1993 Jan. (Box 26)
    - Reader file, 1993 Feb. (Box 26)
    - Reader file, 1993 Mar. (Box 26)
    - Reader file, 1993 Apr. (Box 26)
    - Reader file, 1993 May. (Box 26)
    - Reader file, 1993 June. (Box 26)
    - Reader file, 1993 July. (Box 27)
    - Reader file, 1993 Aug. (Box 27)
    - Reader file, 1993 Sept. (Box 27)
    - Reader file, 1993 Oct. (Box 27)
    - Reader file, 1993 Nov. (Box 27)
    - Reader file, 1993 Dec. (Box 27)
    - Commissioner Clinton V. Turner - correspondence (#1), 1993 Jan-Feb. (Box 27)
    - Deputy Commissioner Donald G. Blankenship (#1), 1993 Jan-Apr. (Box 27)
    - Deputy Commissioner Donald G. Blankenship (#2), 1993 Apr-June. (Box 27)
    - Deputy Commissioner Donald G. Blankenship (#3), 1993 June-Oct. (Box 27)
    - Deputy Commissioner Donald G. Blankenship (#4), 1993 Oct-Dec. (Box 27)
    - Commissioner's Office - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 27)
    - Division Director's memos, 1993. (Box 27)
    - Karen Jackson - Dir. of Human Resources, 1992-1993. (Box 27)
    - Smith, Harriet G., 1993. (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resources, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Hill, Herbert H. (#2), 1993 June-Dec. (Box 28)
    - Hill, Herbert H. (#1), 1993 Jan-June. (Box 28)
    - Hazelwood, M. Wayne, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Seward, Roy E., 1993. (Box 28)
    - Policy, Planning and Agricultural Development - Miscellaneous (#2), 1993 May-Dec. (Box 28)
    - Policy, Analysis and Development - Miscellaneous, 1993 Jan-May. (Box 28)
    - Groundwater, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Layne, Ronald K., 1993. (Box 28)
    - Administration Division - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Radler, Toni L. - Communications Director, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Communications - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Garey, Louis M., 1993. (Box 28)
    - Halbleib, M. Craig, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Martin, Teddy R. - Purchase and Supply Director, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Purchasing - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Blakemore, Betty W., 1993. (Box 28)
    - Consumer Affairs Division - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 28)
    - System Development Priorities, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Jeffries, Larry, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Palmer, Theresa - Finance Office, 1993. (Box 28)
    - Constituent Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Annual Report - Consumer Affairs, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Internal Audit Correction Action Plan - Consumer Affairs, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Ward, Ralph C. - Director, Division of Marketing (#2), 1993 July-Dec. (Box 29)
    - Ward, Ralph C. - Director, Division of Marketing (#1), 1993 Jan-Nov. (Box 29)
    - Marketing Division - Miscellaneous (#2), 1993 Nov-Dec. (Box 29)
    - Marketing Division - Miscellaneous (#1), 1993 Jan-Oct. (Box 29)
    - International Marketing, Office of, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Commodity Services, Office of, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Aquaculture, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Virginia Aquaculture Plan, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Aquaculture and Diversification Loan GuarantyFund, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Farmers Market Network, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Farmers Market Nutrition Program, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Sims, William M. - State Veterinarian (#3), 1993 Oct-Dec. (Box 29)
    - Sims, William M. - State Veterinarian (#2), 1993 Aug-Oct. (Box 29)
    - Sims, William M. - State Veterinarian (#1), 1993 Jan-Aug. (Box 29)
    - Animal Health Division - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Animal Health Laboratory System, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Audit Corrective Plan - Meat and Poultry Inspection Services, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Meat and Poultry Inspection Program Audit Plan, 1993. (Box 29)
    - Animal Health Laboratory Advisory Committee, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Animal Health Laboratory System, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Animal Health Laboratory Fee, 1993. (Box 30)
    - User Fee - National Veterinary Service Laboratories, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Avian Influenza, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Deer Farming Advisory Committee, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Delmarva Poultry Industry, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Poultry Disease Emergency Proclamation, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Scrapie, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Spruill, C. Kermit - Director, Division of Product and Industry Regulation, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Product and Industry Regulation - Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Corn Cyst Nematode, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Crop Insurance, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Dealers in Agricultural Products Law, 1993. (Box 30)
    - House of Delegates, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Delmarva Poulty Industry, 1994. (Box 30)
    - Disaster Relief, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Drought, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Drought Strategic Plan, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Eastern Shore Farmers Market, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Eastern Shore Marketing Coop, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Emergency Evacuation Plan, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Employment Commission, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Environment, Council on the, 1993. (Box 30)
    - Environmental Protecton Agency (EPA), 1993. (Box 30)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 30)
    - EEO Committee, 1993. (Box 31)
    - EEO Programs, 192-1993. (Box 31)
    - State Fair, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Farm Bureau Federation, Virginia, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Family Medical Leave Policy, 1993. (Box 31)
    - Farmers Market Network, Virginia, 1993. (Box 31)